Hi!
Hello?
Ah, there you are.
I didn't notice you there.
How's it going?
Are you having a wonderful Monday?
I need you guys to tell me what your plans are today.
What are you having for dinner?
What are you gonna do?
I need all the information.
I'm collecting data and I'm gonna sell it on the side.
This is still the side business that I have.
Just give it all up.
Probably pasta?
Making Thai tea right now.
That sounds cool.
If I could air fryer potatoes.
Oh, those are nice.
I miss having an air fryer.
I had one for the longest time until I broke it.
You guys are not gonna believe it, but I fucking put my socks in there.
Like the electric socks.
That's how I broke my other pair.
It was a complete accident.
I'm kidding with that one.
Come on, I'm kidding.
That's a lie.
Dude, you know what?
Lying is so much fun, man.
I should start lying more.
I just love lying about random things.
And then saying, ah, just kidding right after.
Oh yeah, it's called rage-bait.
No, no, no.
We're calling it bait-maxing.
Don't forget, or rage-maxing.
Either is good.
Yeah, that's it.
Bob and Zop.
Also, you can stop emailing me and sending me messages on Discord.
I understand what I missed last time, okay?
You don't need to try to spoil me, alright?
Just putting that out there for everyone.
I will figure things out on my own, man.
It was quite aggressive, actually.
I mean, okay, here's the thing.
It's not even a big deal.
It's like there's a menu item where I can press E, you know?
Okay, you don't think I'm gonna see that?
Like, have some faith in me, you know?
Can you be, like, a little more faithful?
It's crazy.
I did not get spoiled in the email, but people did send me emails.
I mean, people send me emails all the time with spoilers.
It's pretty normal.
It was especially bad during Silksong for some reason.
I don't know.
Something about that game made people go crazy.
Who emails anymore?
I mean, I do.
I read my emails.
But I'm all... I'm really bad at responding to them, though.
Because here's what I'll do.
I'll be out walking, right?
And I get a notification on my phone.
Hey, you got an email.
I'm like, okay, let me check what that is.
I'm like, oh, cool.
I'll get back to that.
And then it's marked as red, and I forget about it.
Because I'm doing something in the moment, you know?
It's a horrible habit.
I really shouldn't open any emails on the go.
So you didn't get spoiled.
I mean, it's not even that much of a spoiler if you're talking about pressing E button in the menu.
I know what it is now, okay?
So you can you could say I was spoiled, yes, but it's not really like I would have figured that out.
Are you crazy?
Like, I looked in the menu.
It's like huge.
You don't think I would see that?
You got to have some faith in me, guys.
And man, it's kind of ruined now in a way, right?
Because the hype would have been so crazy when I would have seen that on my own.
So whenever you guys feel the impulse to spoil things, just don't do it because it's not going to be satisfying for me.
Getting the information that way, you know what I mean?
It would have been such a cool moment to have that.
And I, of course, I would have figured it out on my own.
That's all I'm saying.
Just have some faith in me.
That's all.
Cheers.
Yeah, exactly, victorious.
I also got spoiled that the game is pretty much over now.
I also, no, I'm kidding.
I don't know how much I have left, but apparently it's a lot.
No, but I didn't see what the button does, but I have a pretty big suspicion.
I think I know what it is.
Okay, let's do this, guys.
Let's play some Isaac.
For some reason, I feel really good today.
It's hard to explain.
And especially because I didn't take any medicine.
That sounds weird now.
But this is like allergy season, right?
And I take a lot of antihistamines.
And I cannot take antihistamines the next four days, because I have a doctor's appointment where they got to run tests on me.
So the antihistamines will fuck that up, you know?
So they got to figure out if I can take some other medicine for the fucking allergies.
So the next four days, I'm going to be doing a lot of, well, what do you call it?
My nose is going to be runny, okay?
And if I sound nasal, that's why, okay?
I can't take nasal sprays and shit, unfortunately.
So just letting you know, warning you beforehand.
Yeah.
Bless you.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
I actually almost considered calling the doctor saying, can we put this off until after the summer?
Because I really, I got to take these antihistamines.
But for some reason, it's not that bad today.
So, you know, it is what it is.
Let's do this.
It's time for Isaac.
Okay.
Also check this out.
Check out the cross.
Pretty cool.
I missed that last time.
But this is it.
You see, there's a small button up there called E.
It's very hard to miss.
Okay?
Like, dude, win streak of minus 10.
Holy shit.
Oh, I don't want to look at that.
Hold on.
I got up.
Also, why is the music so loud in my ears?
One sec.
I need to fix that.
Oh, whoa, whoa, no, no.
That's for you.
Just for me.
There we go.
There.
Okay.
Let's do this, huh?
I think, oh, I never noticed you can see the little familiar in the back there on Eulith.
So let me try this.
Whoa, okay.
What the fuck is happening here?
Wait, what is actually happening?
What?
Yeah, this is exactly what I thought.
Well, not exactly, but you know, in that area.
Oh my God, listen to the sound.
Oh man, this moment was kind of ruined, knowing beforehand, just a little bit, you know?
But this is cool still.
I think this is cool.
So apparently we got alternate versions of these characters.
So wait, minus one, two and four, minus one, three and four.
So we have less speed, broken wings, hemoptysis.
Is this like an even harder mode, I guess?
That's probably what it is.
So it seems like I can't fly, broken wings, hemoptysis.
I'm not sure what that means.
Some kind of medical condition.
We got to try it.
Oh, wow.
All right.
Okay, let me get ready here.
Let me just move this out of the way.
Prepare the setup.
We're gonna be a sasal maxing.
Wait.
Yeah, okay.
So what's happening?
What?
Oh my God, we have brimstone from the go.
But it's very narrow.
Looks like we have a small... I don't know what that is, like a little spray.
Short range attack before the big one.
I mean, am I crazy?
Or is this better?
Ah, we can't fly though.
That's the big downside.
So you actually trade your wings for a brimstone.
A worse brimstone.
Let's go in here.
Belly button?
I'm pretty sure I've never had that, so I don't know why the description is there.
And I was holding two trinkets at a time.
Spawns one random trinket on pickup.
Oh, wait, I have had this.
Hold capacitor.
Active items no longer gain charge from completing rooms.
20% chance to spawn a little battery as a room clear reward.
Is that just me or is that bad?
Like, I'd rather have normal items compared to batteries.
But, I mean, let's just try it.
I cannot go in there because I can't fly.
I still start with the fool.
Let's see what else has changed.
Oh, shit.
I'm scared here.
How am I going to do this without taking damage?
I can't.
I'm actually going to take damage here.
Nice.
That's it.
Okay, I like this one more.
All right, we can have two.
And the way to change that was... Oh, no.
Whoops.
Double tap.
I don't remember.
How come that's not explained in the start, you know?
What we got here?
Coupon.
Pill.
Really want that coupon.
Well, let's be honest.
Getting that on the first floor is... brother.
Kind of impossible.
I cannot believe that.
Is this a short range?
Oh, it is.
Oh, nice.
The stars.
Oh, right.
Well, that was a waste.
For a second, I was like, oh, yeah, that's going to take me to the planetarium.
Why am I so bad at this game?
I swear to God.
You know what?
The hardest parts of this game are the inanimate objects.
It's just next level, the heart,
because it's like counterintuitive.
Whoa, nice.
The gym has been activated.
You know what that means?
It doesn't mean anything.
You know what?
Like this brimstone here is pretty good.
It's just as good as the other one, it feels like.
Because it's not really hard to hit with it, you know?
I cannot believe that just happened.
The short range attack is interesting.
Box, give me a blue heart.
Oh, I did say red heart, didn't it?
We got a pill, though.
Range down.
But that's not going to matter, is it?
Yeah, we have infinite range.
And paperclip, I like a lot, too.
I think I'd rather have that.
Yeah, these two.
The fool.
I'm going to clear everything.
I'm going to start focusing here.
Whoa, it pushes them back.
Wait, what?
Wait a minute.
Am I marking these enemies for explosion?
Oh, wait a second now.
Aha!
Isn't that interesting?
Okay.
It's so weird being a sasyl and not flying.
Huh.
Okay, let me find secret rooms.
See if I had gotten hit by that again.
Okay, let's destroy this.
Hey, more bombs, that's good.
You know what the cool thing about Finding a Visig is?
Like, you have these really shitty runs.
But then you hear this music and you start a new run and all the possibilities are there again, you know?
You just know.
Now it's going to be different.
This time.
This time I'll do it differently.
And I never do, but you always get that feeling of this time, you know?
This run.
It's a nice feeling.
I'm going to take this.
Yep.
And maybe even blow this up.
There we go.
The master at work.
Oh, that's very nice.
Instantly destroys the fires.
I wonder how much, like pure...
Oh my god.
Imagine a third time.
I may have actually uninstalled the game if that would have happened.
I could destroy this.
Check this out, we're going to do this.
Fuck, I am actually a god at this game.
Holy shit.
Perfection.
Absolute perfection.
There's no other way to put it.
Let's leave.
So wait, the fool?
Death?
I think I'll keep the fool.
Okay.
Cheers.
I'm curious to see if anything is changing in these levels.
Now that we're in this sort of weird mode.
That attack is super good.
Whoa!
It's almost better than the...
It's not better than the brimstone, but you know.
Just saying.
Wait, he just got turned into a burning version.
Because he ran into the fire.
We're going to go slow.
Dude, I love this short range attack.
I think my base attack is less damage than standard assasal.
That's for you.
Now they're going to get exploded.
Oh, it doesn't last a long time.
Interesting.
So I guess you want to use the button press.
For the charge up as well on the same enemy.
Like you want to walk in like this.
Oh, there's no enemies.
Okay.
Load up.
Three keys.
Huge chest.
Holy shit.
Oh!
Wow.
There's the boss.
I think we should do it now.
Yeah, we're going to mark him.
Oh, but these are dangerous to get close to.
Do it.
No!
It spreads!
No way!
Okay, it's even better than I thought.
Matchbook.
Another matchstick.
Wait, can I have two matchsticks?
Oh, I can't.
That's too sad.
I think we're going to do angel maxing.
I love that term.
That's shit!
Okay, nice.
Give me that.
Dude, we have 15 bombs.
Time to open some windows.
Fuck, I am just incredible.
Nothing has ever been done like this before.
The way I'm doing it now.
This is some next level stuff.
Take notes, people.
Wait!
Oh, I thought I was slowly regrowing my wings.
I thought the little, you know, the little animation there was my wings coming out.
Maybe I can repair my broken wings.
Bam, bam, bam, bam.
What do we got here?
Our glass is pretty dang good.
I don't have a lot of money though.
I could blow up the machine to get it if I wanted.
Maybe I will.
Although that is kind of, you know, anti getting the machine higher in number.
I can't speak English.
You know what I mean.
I'm trying to donate more to the machine as well.
But then I go ahead and do stuff like this, you know.
Hold up.
This one's bad.
This is the...
Uh, reroll all items.
Ew.
I don't like it.
Unless I have shit items.
What items do I have?
You know what?
Dude, I actually don't hate it.
Mystery egg.
Following familiar the hatches when Isaac takes damage, spawning a permanently charmed monster.
The strength of the monster is increased with each consecutive room cleared without it breaking.
Okay.
Ah, range is useless on me.
Yo, that was worth it.
Just for that.
Wait, can I...
I can't keep stepping on this, right?
Okay, I was about to say that would be broken as hell.
Ooh!
Poor man's dad's key!
Not bad.
What the hell is that?
Scapular.
When damage down to the last half-heart automatically gain a soul heart?
Yeah.
I like.
Probably a better way of doing this.
Okay, secrets.
Could be one here.
Maybe one here.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
To the rock!
Oh, sick.
Very nice.
I'm just gonna try a bunch of walls.
I wonder if they are close together.
No, actually they're not always close together.
I think this one is a...
Ah, no, wait, there was a poop there.
Maybe not.
Oh!
I never opened that?
What's wrong with me?
There we go.
Dude, it's going really well.
Getting a lot of good buffer here.
I think we can afford to go into the curse room.
I didn't think they would get that close to me that fast.
He walked into the fire.
Plus two damage for the room.
I do like that.
Oh, shit.
Ah, no problem.
But I think I would rather use the pool to get out.
Then again, I can also save the pool for the strange door.
Questions, questions.
I think I'm gonna...
No, here's the plan.
We're gonna get a win streak going.
I don't know what the plan is actually.
We're just gonna do random shit.
Just get out of there and save the HP.
I can't look at the amount of losses in a row, you know?
We gotta just work on winning something.
And then when we have at least one win, we're gonna try and get back and do the thing we lost to last time.
The 2D side-scroller part.
That's the plan.
But I could also change it as we go.
We'll see how I feel.
The plan is open.
Here we go.
Plotted caves, best soundtrack.
Oh, the range is not that long on that one.
Ooh.
Fuck.
Yeah, it definitely feels like I'm doing less damage with this compared to normal, as they do.
Yeah, I have to get used to just holding the button after tagging them.
Like that.
Shit.
Oh, God.
Wait, can I bounce back the projectiles?
Oh, my God!
Okay, that's even better!
So much utility here.
Spread it.
Oh, yeah, look at that!
Hey, that's actually amazing.
Love this character.
I mean, anything SA's or Adjacent is making me happy.
Alright, let's not go in there.
Not yet.
Spread it to everyone.
Wow.
I mean, you just start with Brimstone.
It's insane.
Brother Bobby.
Fires basic tears.
Sure.
What are these buttons, though?
Oh, okay.
Oh, no.
It's a very short range.
Ooh, I think I see a secret room.
Right here.
Let's check the other rooms, just to see.
Looks good so far.
Still looks good.
I think this may be it.
Let's do it.
Damn!
Unfortunate.
Oh, we're rich.
Twenty-seven gold coins.
Ooh!
Good reaction there.
I need more tears.
The charge speed is painful.
Raise stock.
Ooh, that's good.
I think I like that.
Minus one range.
Thanks.
I'll take that.
I'll take this.
And maybe I'll even... You know what?
Let's donate!
Instead of talking it, let's do the walking, too.
I'm gonna fill up that box, dammit.
I think I see a secret room.
Nope, never mind.
There's rocks in the way.
I think I'm getting like... It's almost like I get this sort of sixth sense for the secret rooms.
Could also be confirmation bias.
I'm well aware of that.
But it feels like I am getting better, you know?
Ah!
Fuck you!
Wait, are you my friend, or what's happening here?
Why are you not taking damage?
I'm confused!
Wait, are they my friends or not?
Oh, wait.
Oh, they are my...
What's happening?
Wait a second.
Is it the mystery egg?
Yeah, it is.
Oh my god, okay.
That was so confusing.
I get it now.
Dude, they're gonna do a lot of damage.
No!
Rest in peace.
You were nice for as long as you were there.
Maybe we can make it hatch again.
Okay, let's do the boss!
Chubby!
Okay, maybe I should just start marking these guys.
Forgot!
Wow.
Somehow I did not take damage there, I don't understand how.
It's definitely harder to do this.
Compared to Azazel.
It feels like I'm just not doing very much damage.
Oh, here we go.
Oh wait, do I do more damage as well to straight up?
When they're marked.
I think that may be the case.
A bar of soap.
That is just so incredibly plain.
But I need more tears.
So I'll take it.
We're not done on this floor.
I got things to do.
Sights to see, fools to demolish.
Nope.
Maybe here.
I have so many bombs.
Just play it safe.
It is a little tricky to hit them with the tiny laser.
Okay.
I thought I was gonna land right in the center of that.
Can you imagine?
Did I check this one?
I think I checked this one already.
Uh, yeah, I did, I did.
I think I checked this one also.
Let's go up here.
Maybe here?
That's a long shot, though.
Yeah.
Hmm.
Zero coins.
Because I donated all of it.
Dude, where are these secret rooms, though?
Ah, maybe over here.
On the right side.
This place I didn't check.
Right here.
What?
Okay.
Never mind, I don't have a sixth sense.
I lied.
Apparently I'm clueless.
Uh...
Let me do a really far-fetched idea here.
No?
What about here?
Brother man.
Okay, I guess...
Man, these are really hidden.
I have no idea.
I was doing so well with the secret rooms in this run.
And then all of a sudden, what happened?
I lost my powers.
Maybe here.
Last attempt.
Fuck!
Unbelievable!
That was like six bombs out the window.
Okay.
67% angel chance.
Not bad at all.
This may not be worth it.
Let's find out.
Not really worth it.
Uh...
Okay, good.
Let's try and hatch this egg.
No!
Whoo!
Good dodge.
I think the egg got hatched.
And it was a shitty one.
Let's do left side.
Yo!
Yeah, you... marking is the way.
Yeah, I'm having trouble hitting.
I wonder if there's a way to increase the... the girth of my attack.
Whoopsie.
Show me the goods.
What is that?
Uh... Himalacria.
Oh, that's the one that replaces.
Tiers with large arcing bloodshots that burst into a spray of smaller bloodshots on impact.
Large shots dealing increased damage, whatever it is, fire rate.
Honestly, I may actually try it.
Just because I'm not a big fan of the... of the very narrow laser, you know?
Fuck it, let's do it.
Oh, it's actually super good!
I thought it... I guess last time I had the one where I was controlling it in the air and it was super confusing.
This is just like throwing a bomb.
And I'll have crazy damage.
I like this.
Forgot!
Careful!
Nice.
Okay, I can't hit with this.
Nevermind.
This sucks.
Let's give it a couple more tries, though.
Dude, it's doing nothing!
I made a mistake!
Did I lose my marking ability?
Oh, I think I did.
Oh, well, I fucked up, guys.
It's all in the name of experimentation.
I mean, the damage is not that bad, as long as I can hit.
But it's still pretty terrible.
All things considered.
Yeah, when I saw the frickin' arc, I was like, oh yeah, it's gonna be like a bomb.
But no, it's not a bomb.
Okay, we found the boss.
Let's check it out!
It's CQ!
CQ, come in!
This is W-3-H-O.
I forgot the actual designation.
Calling Pensacola.
Oh, wait, we gotta hit him from the back, of course.
This is how that works.
Yeah, good.
Solid hit.
Wait, that was a bad one.
Yeah, I want my old attack back!
I done goofed!
It's not the end of the world, but, you know, it is kinda the end of the world.
No, Angel!
Brother...
67, though.
Spawn 7 random coins.
Let's see what it is, then.
Wait!
I was about to say, wasn't I able to hold two trinkets, but that was before I did the flipperoo.
So, no.
I guess not.
Wait, what happened?
Chances spawn a bomb each time.
Ah, right.
Right.
That's it.
We're going back, though.
Right here.
Guarantee.
That there's nothing there.
Ah, I should have walked in here and checked.
You see that?
There's a little gap there.
I could have known.
Mistakes were made.
Okay, man, I'm one-shotting these guys.
It's...
Feels good.
I'm not gonna lie.
Okay, okay.
Not one-shotting these guys, though.
Why am I doing that?
Jesus!
Could maybe stab a little bit.
Nah, not with blue and black cards.
That's a bad idea.
What a shot, though.
Did you see that?
We're not gonna be lacking any bombs.
Dude, I'm a diagonal master.
Child's heart?
No, I don't need that.
Love getting all these bombs.
Means I can just randomly check for things right here.
Maybe here?
Okay, fine.
Fine.
It's not north, either.
It could be in here.
Wow!
Not bad!
Okay, blow this up.
Very good.
About time, though.
Angel?
No.
No angel for me.
So that's one of them.
But feels like they're close together, but not too close.
So maybe within, like, a three-room circle, if you know what I mean.
Like, a radius of three rooms.
Spreading outward from the qua- I'm totally pulling that out of my ass right now.
But we gotta work from something, you know?
Could be over here.
Can it be right next to each other?
I mean, it could, I guess.
Definitely not that room.
Nah, we got seven bombs.
Let's just save the rest.
We found one room that's cool.
Moving on.
It is what it is.
A hundred percent angel now.
I mean, we can't fuck this one up, can we?
Dude, please open up your mouth!
Before I lose my mind.
I got hit twice there because they just refused to do it.
That was so frustrating.
Oh, no.
How the fuck are you supposed to dodge that?
He's fast.
A pill!
Haha, that's massive!
Scary.
The sun!
Oh, that's massive.
I should actually...
use it early, I guess, so I can see the secret rooms.
But it's kind of a waste to use it, but no, use it now.
Fuck it.
Just let me see everything.
Okay, let's go this way.
Oh, what a chain reaction.
Lead pencil?
Oh, okay.
I mean, that's kind of...
It's going to happen rarely, though.
Yeah, we don't shoot that fast.
How fast do I shoot?
Yeah, it's very slow.
Nice.
Good to get some more of those.
Still 100% Angel.
And we have a great buffer.
I think I should just go straight for the boss.
That looks crazy when it happens.
Oh, I mean, I have eight keys.
Wait, why did I... That doesn't make any sense, what I just did.
That's a bad idea.
How do I... Oh, shit.
Ooh!
Wow!
Those things move faster, too, I think.
Compared to the regular sized bombs.
Oi!
Wait, one, two, three, four...
Okay, here we go.
You ready?
Boom!
Yo!
Not bad at all, huh?
Oh, shit.
What a bomb that was.
Sir!
Oh, no, I missed it!
Oh, that was a big attack.
Meat.
More damage is good.
And Angel to boot.
Whoa, I get to choose all of these.
The prism I'm not a big fan of.
Breath of life!
Holding use depletes the charge bar.
Isaac becomes invincible.
Touching enemies while invincible summons light beams.
Touching an enemy at the same time the charge bar is empty fires a four-way beam.
Holding use after the charge bar is empty causes continual damage to Isaac.
Hmm...
Trinity shield.
That's a good one!
That's a solid one.
Jesus juice.
The prism could actually be kind of crazy, because we have quite a high damage output.
So if we do get it through the prism...
Whoo!
Especially with the 15 shots amplification, you know.
But Jesus juice is just straight up good for stats.
But...
This one.
Oh, man, I want all of it.
I think I'll take... We have pretty good damage, right?
We don't need range, so range is actually useless on me.
So fuck that one.
It's either this one or the prism for me.
The prism is a bit more...
What do you call it?
High risk, high reward.
This one is more safe.
I think I'm taking this.
Yeah, play it more safe.
And then we're gonna blow this guy up.
What's up, dude?
Let's get ready for the big one.
Haha!
Dude, the big one is really big!
The big one is legitimately big!
Like, we have to turn this build around the 15 shots.
That's what we need to do.
It's all about the 15.
Crazy stuff.
Mom's bracelet.
That's good!
Takes us to 2 out of 3 on Yes Mother?
I take that.
Oh, we get a restock!
Yo!
3 out of 3 on Yes Mother!
I'll take it!
Okay, so we have a knife now.
That's what that...
Ooh, I want that too.
Can we somehow get that?
Uh, the chariot.
Let me see what else we got here.
I don't want to buy anything accidentally here.
Uh, the magician.
Death.
Two of hearts.
I mean, may as well use that there.
Of hearts.
Oh wait, I thought it would drop two hearts on the floor.
Never mind.
That's the other one.
Which one do I keep?
Magician could be sick with mine, right?
Big shot, all homing?
Yeah.
Let's go with that one.
I like.
I'll come back for the...
There's options.
If I can gather the money.
This is the plan.
I think maybe right here, but let's check the other sides.
Nope.
Okay, it's not that one.
And let's not forget, we can do this now.
Uh, let me just re-read that, just to confirm.
Grab and pick up a rock or other stationary obstacle.
Press an attack button to throw it, smashing it and dealing damage to enemy struck.
I wonder if I can, uh, break holes in walls.
With that.
Probably not.
Uh, get in here.
Nope.
We still have a couple of rooms to explore, though.
Oh shit, uh...
Wait, can I just put it down?
Gently.
I wanted to block this thing, you know?
I don't know if that helped, maybe it did help.
Bombs galore.
Right here.
Okay, then right here.
Wait, I'm an idiot.
I can see the entire map.
Well, you know what happens.
Sometimes you miss that.
I maybe want to go in there.
I really need money!
Sad.
Jump!
Oh my goodness.
That's the big one.
Oh, what a room.
Uh, come on.
I'm an idiot!
Haha, I got you, rage bait.
Bait maxing, I got you, didn't I?
Haha.
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
Got you there.
Hahahaha.
Uh...
Oh my god!
What the heck?
Really?
Okay, dude.
We're taking...
Okay, I thought I just used the card.
I was about to say, we're opening all the skulls.
Go, go, go!
Imagine I find flying.
Then I'm almost a sizzle.
Except I lost the ability to use my laser.
Um...
Go.
I'm trying to understand what the advantages of going the other way.
Through those other rooms.
Maybe it's simply...
I mean, you get to fight different bosses.
Maybe that unlocks different things.
Whoa!
Oh my god!
That's so good!
That's so nice.
Huge attack.
Uh, what?
Ah.
Let's see how it is.
No!
A pill.
Ah, that's not good.
I'll use the world here.
Kind of want to find the other key piece.
See, I think I'm drowsy right now.
Oh man, that was close.
Um, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Be good.
No!
I mean, it's not that bad, I guess.
Wait, I need to see, how does that work again?
Finds a pushable TNT barrel.
Using the item again, didn't it?
Got it.
Oh, it's not that pushable, it's very heavy.
It's a good way to check for secrets, I guess.
Not that we need to, we got the world.
The jar!
Let's not forget, if we buy, it gets restocked.
There's really nothing.
Donate!
It's for a good cost.
There we go.
551.
No thanks.
You know, I could have just placed the TNT there and exploded it when she got close.
That's actually a strategy.
Like that!
Dude, it's actually not that bad!
Wait, can he destroy that from a distance?
Hahaha!
Oh!
It's the other one!
This guy!
Yee!
Whoo!
If I hadn't killed him there, I would have gotten hit, I think.
Good.
I think I'm just going to go ahead and do the boss.
Wait, no, it's mom!
Fuuuuuuck!
I forgot it was mom.
Fuck me.
I was going to at least get the possibility to teleport out of here.
Shit.
What the hell was that?
Can you stop throwing that?
You're making me nervous!
I'm going to take this one this time, just to switch it up.
Angel time, though.
Hey, at least we get to...
Dude, can you stop throwing the bombs?
Okay, well, there we go.
Both key pieces.
What is that?
Trisagion.
Smite Die enemy.
Replaces tears with large piercing bursts of holy energy.
The bursts deal reduced damage, but can damage enemies multiple times as they pass through.
I like that!
That seems really good.
More speed, nice.
Stable?
Yeah, why not?
Oh!
The 15 rule, 15 second rule is off the charts!
I'm still shooting slow, though.
That's the only downside here.
Okay, I can't leave, but we have a key now, right?
That's probably cool enough.
I forget exactly where that goes.
Wow!
Okay, we can't see the world anymore.
Oh, it doesn't one-shot them?
I thought for sure this would be a big-ass attack, but no.
Hmm, maybe I hate it.
Yeah, I don't know about this, guys!
We may have to still stick to the 15 second rule.
Yay!
But the fact that they spread outwards afterwards is kind of cool.
Oh, it's not actually infinite range, it's stopping at a certain point and then spreading out.
Huh?
Oh, I didn't see the spikes, shit.
They fooled me with that one.
Let's actually try this here.
Whoa!
I'm in trouble, in terms of HP.
It's not good.
Open up.
Hello.
Your turn.
Let's just keep trying the bomb.
Jesus!
I don't think I like this new attack I got, guys.
It feels worse.
Especially because I'm shooting so slow.
Dude, we're so low on HP, we gotta get that heart.
If we can, hopefully it's not on some island.
Okay, it's not.
I got flies on my side.
It looks really cool, though.
I have such low DPS.
Except when that one happens, then it's really good.
Oh, nice.
Oh, what the...
Okay, so one, two, we're gonna do this.
Four, five, six.
Seven.
Okay, here we go.
Wow!
Question mark.
Range and lock-up.
Eh.
Honestly, not a big fan of that.
I think I'm just gonna keep going.
Down the hatch.
I'm going to the higher stages.
Remember, the only goal we originally had for this run was just to win.
It's just about winning, that's it.
Regain some sanity.
If we can make that happen, then I'm happy.
Dude, I missed my original attack on this character.
First it got turned into the artillery, and then it got turned into this, and I feel like it's gotten worse every time.
Which is sad.
This place looks insane.
Two health.
Goodnight.
That's nice.
I am a little rich, I could afford to do a bit of this.
Come on, be good to me.
I need health item or something.
Or maybe something that gives me extra tears, that would be huge.
I don't care about that.
Come on, you're my friend.
Is that how you treat your friend?
I mean, bombs are gonna be useful damage-wise.
But still.
Dang.
We're gonna spend all our money.
Not even a heart?
Okay, well.
Why does it always happen right when I say it?
It's almost like a universal law of nature.
Okay.
I actually blow this one up, too.
Mmm, yep.
I think I have decent HP right now.
Not too bad.
Oh, shit!
Neat!
Can we?
And it's gone.
What a room, though.
That was a short joy I had there.
Dude, what even is this place?
I've just stopped questioning.
Like, what is happening in this game?
Dude, how on earth are you gonna survive this?
Yep.
Huge, that came in clutch.
Soul hearts is so clutch.
Also, how did I lose a bunch of red hearts just now?
Like, without going through my blue hearts.
Because I just picked up two blue hearts and I had one blue heart.
So, what the hell?
The fuck was that?
Maybe they only damaged red hearts, some of these enemies?
Now we got one of these again.
Let's try and hold onto it for two floors.
I think that's maybe when something happens.
Maybe, like, here?
No?
Okay.
Oh, wait, wrong way.
Oh, actually, actually, yes!
Hey!
Nice!
I'm glad I went in there.
Oh, didn't even die from that.
Six...
Seven...
Eight...
Where's the boss?
I mean, I have good range.
Whoa!
Dude!
What the fuck is this?!
Jesus!
How is he not dying?
I don't understand.
Oh, he's a friend.
It makes sense.
You're a friend.
Three random cards.
Uh, give me something good.
No, troll bombs.
No, I don't want this.
Okay.
Let's just get in.
It lives.
Oh, that's my friend.
Yeah, suck on that big one.
Okay, damage is actually not that bad.
That was not bad at all.
And we did it without taking damage somehow.
Higher stages.
Cathedral.
I need a buffer.
So I can see what happens on the next floor with his heart.
I could just shoot this way and just hit the... the bounce hit him, you know?
Yeah, that's actually a way to play pretty safe.
Just keep shooting.
That's actually the best thing I can do.
Wait, there's... Why is there a machine like that here?
Oh no!
I didn't mean to kill you!
Sorry, friend!
That was a mistake.
I'm sorry.
That just cost me a lot of HP.
Dude, this thing in the corner keeps messing with my head.
Thinking it's an enemy.
No!
I didn't mean to enter.
But it's okay, I guess.
Blackheart.
Nah, we lost it anyway.
I forgot that it's one heart damage here.
That's not looking good, I'm gonna be honest with you.
This is a rough one.
Almost no HP.
Wait, I keep missing a... door over here.
Jesus Christ.
No, not the static object hitting me!
Fucking hate that!
Goddamn inanimate objects.
Enemies?
Okay.
Whew!
Give me healing.
Heal me!
Uh...
The shop, sure.
Okay, okay.
Damage is decent.
Oh, wow, wow, wow!
Fuck!
Wait, how am I...
I'm somehow protected!
Something is happening here!
Why am I being protected?
Is it that one?
No.
Is it just a Trinity Shield?
Maybe it's just that, actually.
I just had it in the right configuration.
Huh, alright.
Trinity Shield, good.
I'm glad I picked it up.
Oh crap, oh crap!
There goes my buffer!
And my run, pretty much.
This may be the end.
There's too much crap!
Oh god, kill the bombs!
Secret discovered!
Ow!
Whew, wow!
Oh, that's massive!
That's Omega massive!
That's...
better than what I have, actually.
Yeah, make some flies.
Boss discovered!
Guys?
This is it.
Wish me luck!
It's time for his sack!
What the hell?
Oh, okay.
Give me the big attack!
There it is.
Wait, what?
It's not going too well, actually.
I will say that.
I admit it.
Yeah, baby!
W!
Let's do this!
Wait, wait, wait, we're not done!
Fuck, I thought that was the end.
Something icky.
Fuck, I'm not ready for this.
Oh, right!
We also have that going.
Oh, my God.
Well, I think we're done.
Clicker!
I mean, I'm tempted to do it, honestly.
Libra?
Yikes!
That's horrible.
I'll take that.
I think I'll take this one as well.
Yeah, no thanks.
I don't think I want this either.
I need HP.
I think this is the end of my run here.
Yeah.
Man.
Fuck.
I forgot there was more.
It's minus 11 now!
Oh, that's so rough!
But you know what?
Let's actually try playing with this without changing the tiers.
Because
it was kind of sad just replacing the whole shtick of the character, you know?
Ipecac!
Are you fucking serious right now?
Fine!
Wait, what?
Wait, it's...
Oh, I still have my original!
Okay!
So you can't trust the game when it says replaces tiers?
It's not consistent!
Uh-uh-uh!
Fine.
Good to know though.
So it's explosive damage, so I can just...
Oh!
Ah-ha!
That's nice!
What's up, fool?
Open up.
Say, ah!
Okay.
What's up, fools?
Dude, I'm loving this.
This is a good one.
Eat big cock.
Dude, I'm just gonna be able to destroy everything.
I'm eating rocks.
Hey!
That's why you eat rocks, kids.
Always eat your rocks.
Let's remember, don't go down that hatch afterwards.
It's illegal.
Blue map.
Three blue hearts?
No thanks.
Yikes.
That's good.
What if I destroy this guy?
Oh, I can't.
It works on close!
Yo, that's even better!
Wow!
Tell me that ain't sick.
Don't go down there.
Holy crap.
We need to not take damage now.
This is a golden opportunity.
I will say, though, the enemies do not get marked anymore.
That's the only downside here I see.
Oh!
Okay, so when you do the charged attack, the explosion damages yourself.
Good to know.
It just seemed like maybe it wouldn't, because it doesn't do it in close range, which is kind of counterintuitive.
Nothing there.
Oh!
I didn't mean to take that, but it's actually fine.
You best believe I'm going to destroy every rock in here.
And I may even hold on to the fool.
I mean, 25 coins already?
Grants are following Familia with a randomized appearance, fire rate, damage and bonus tier effects.
Familia's traits are randomized at the start of each new floor.
Okay.
I'll take it.
We can take another buffer here.
Well, not really a buffer on this character, but you know what I mean.
Yeah, now what I mean.
Wait, did he just have... Oh, it's my Familia.
I was like, he has electricity.
But no, he doesn't.
Wow!
How lucky is that?
Yo, I can find secrets like this as well!
100%.
I just realized.
Yeah!
Oh, wow!
Okay, dude, this is actually out of control.
This run is gonna be nuts.
I can tell you that right now.
We're gonna look everywhere.
Okay.
Clear.
Wow, that's nice.
I can destroy two at once.
Can I destroy three at once?
Not quite.
Actually, four at once is what I meant.
So this part is clear.
I need to develop a strategy where I'm just consistently checking one side at a time here.
There we go!
Oh!
I will give him all my money.
No, thanks.
See, now you're...
No, keep the fool.
That's good.
One more of those, please.
Oh, man, you're really making me rethink my fool here.
Uh...
I'll take this just for the boss, so I can maybe reroll, and then I'll come back for the fool.
That's the plan.
Yeah.
Let's see what we get here.
Larry...
Junior...
We got poisons.
Let's see.
Cancel spawn a red heart when taking damage.
Mmm...
No.
Ah!
I should have taken it.
Okay, I mean...
Extra...
You know, that's not bad, actually.
Getting some more tears?
Kind of huge.
And check this out.
Hey, hey, hey!
Yo...
This is gonna be a bonkers run.
Let's go!
Kidding.
Come on.
You think I forgot the fool?
Did you now?
You really think I did?
Thanks...
Wait, I have four coins.
Come on.
Hey!
Dude, is this the craziest first floor of all time?
Holy shit, look at my HP!
What the fuck?
It has never been this good?
Holy shit.
Uh, no.
This way.
And then right, right, down.
Oh, wait, wait.
No, no, no.
Back, back, back.
Keep going.
Kind of want to go... No.
We are going to the strange door.
And we're gonna fuck shit up in there.
Three coins?
I'm using two of them.
Okay.
I meant, uh, keys.
Ooh, that's massive for me!
Fast charge speed is big!
Also, I should be looking for secrets even right now.
Come on.
Unnecessary.
I almost used the fool there instinctively, but I didn't do it.
Oh, you know what?
I should be doing this.
Ah, it's only the first one that blows up.
Okay, never mind.
I thought I had a more efficient way of destroying rocks.
Whoa!
What?
A black heart just like that now?
What did I get to deserve all this?
A boomerang?
It's actually not too bad.
But it's not really that cool either.
Maybe.
We'll see.
Ah, mistakes!
I realized a millisecond before I released the button.
It's like when you play chess and you know your move is bad.
The millisecond after you let go of the mouse, you know?
It's actually a good opportunity to start to document the locations of secret rooms.
So, one of them is in the middle, as is expected.
Shit.
Oh my God!
Just like that, I mean...
What's with this run?
I feel blessed.
I don't deserve it.
Actually, who am I kidding?
I do.
I deserve it.
Imagine I can also blast my way into this room.
That would be too much.
A little brimstone.
That's two out of three on conjoined.
If I get another one, it's gonna be the three-way split, no?
That's what that one does.
So, one of them is right smack in the center.
I mean, I'm just gonna check everything, I guess.
I may have checked this one already, but...
Just to be safe.
I'm having an absolute blast right now, guys.
This is like, frickin'...
peak gaming nirvana feeling right now.
Like, everything I love about gaming is happening right now.
In this very moment.
I'm feeling it.
What a great feeling.
Of course we destroyed the pots!
But wait, some of these have bombs in them, right?
Maybe we do range it on those.
Yeah, played safe.
This room has been obliterated.
Let's look for secrets all around here.
Ah!
Whoops.
Oh my goodness.
Okay, one is very much out of the way.
Coins.
I can also go grab the boomerang.
Honestly, I don't need the boomerang.
It's gonna be too much.
This guy gives battery, right?
I don't want batteries.
I'm saving my money.
Okay, so here's what we're gonna do.
I'm gonna take a picture.
What the...
Wait, why does my screen turn into that?
Hold on, something's wrong here.
No, no.
Picture this one.
Thank you.
Oh no, no, no.
Make it so I can see it.
Thank you.
Dude, for some reason my print screen thingy is not working very well in Binding of Isaac.
It's just not.
Oh, that's very tiny.
There we go.
That's number two.
Here.
Okay, time for the boss.
Our job is done here.
Gorglings!
Never mind, they do get marked!
Hallelujah!
The mark is real.
And we even get one of these.
Dude, what is happening in this run?
I don't understand.
I don't get it.
I would say both are good, man.
Shot speed is useless, but extra tiers is massive.
Now it costs three, that's fine.
Yeah.
We take those.
Absolutely.
No question about it.
Hell yeah, onward.
Let me see the charge speed now.
Oh my god.
Oh no, it's the mushrooms that explode.
It's not the jars.
I just realized.
They have like swamp gas in them or something.
Louisiana gas.
You know what else happens in Louisiana?
You know it.
I know it.
Another fucking die shard!
Dude.
I think Azazel is just in general...
more lucky.
The science speaks for itself.
Another black heart?
I mean, what the fuck is that?
A card against humanity fills every floor tile with poop?
What?
Well,
money problem has been solved.
This is fucking nuts.
Imagine I have that item that makes me get more stuff when I destroy poops.
I'm taking this for now.
I'll come back for the fool.
And don't worry, I'm not going to forget it, if that's what you're thinking.
Oh, Eowas!
It's just getting better and better.
Every item I get is better than the last.
Let's look for... Oh, wait, I can't see any decorations in there.
Maybe in here.
Nothing decorative about this.
Oh, he exploded on death.
Whoops.
Decoration.
Could be this grass right here.
No, don't do that to me.
Oh, that's evil.
Man, I really want to get in there.
There's so much crap.
Or we do that.
Wait, how am I doing that?
Am I just...?
Oh, I'm pushing them like that.
Yo!
Oh, I can't reach it.
Hahaha.
Not bad.
I got to look for a floor decoration.
I think, uh...
No, I don't see one.
A locky pen.
Okay, this one.
Yeah!
Okay, it was a bit of grass.
A bit of dry grass.
Seem to work.
Oh, wait, that's not an enemy.
It's Bumbo.
Wanders around consuming coin pickups.
Levels up as it consumes coins, gaining new abilities.
We're going to get a lot of coins, though.
This is going to be kind of cool.
We're going to level this guy all the way up.
Kind of curious to see what that does.
Oh, yeah, take those!
Take those!
That's good!
Good job!
No way!
Oh, okay, it's the same secret room.
Once again, one of the secret rooms is very centralized.
Teleport 2.0.
I'm excited about that one, actually.
Finally got an active.
Okay, let's try.
No, I'm not going to go in there.
Not yet.
That was kind of dumb.
Okay, that's good.
I was a little too big, anyway.
You want to pick it up?
Bumbo?
There you go.
Consume.
No.
Chance to inflict burn on an enemy when entering a new room.
Increases with luck.
I got two luck!
I like this more, I think.
Fuck the mushroom.
Ah, damn it!
It exploded in my face.
Less speed, no thanks.
Oh, I should have let Bumbo take that.
Potato peeler.
Consumes a red heart container to grant a permanent cube of meat.
I'll take that.
I'll take this.
Whatever that is.
Doesn't matter for me, I think.
Speed.
This one.
So, I need to understand this teleport thing.
Teleport to an uncleared room in order of priority.
So, if I clear everything except the boss, that means we're going to get to the boss.
I don't know what this first room is, though.
Like the square.
The white room.
Or something.
I don't know if that's a thing, but it sounds like a thing.
Let me actually try that.
Okay, so check it out.
We got two rooms left.
We got a curse room and boss room.
Oh, okay, so after the boss comes secret.
But it's the grey secret.
Hold on a minute.
We have the white secret.
Which means...
Ah, but wait a minute.
What about... does it say curse room as well?
It does!
Okay, okay, but that's after...
Alright.
So, we're going to do the boss now.
And we should be teleported to...
the grey secret.
Oh, god.
Easy.
Little chat!
Familiar drops a half red heart.
I don't know if I like that.
Also, where did my...
Didn't I have a re-roll thingy?
What the...
Wait a minute.
Ah, shit.
If I leave now, this may disappear.
We got to go in here.
Uh, goat head.
That's... interesting, actually.
I don't like guppy stuff.
I'll take this.
Fuck the other one.
That's such a bad item, like...
Why would you ever take that?
Maybe... okay.
Maybe if the guppy... like, 3 out of 3 is good.
I just don't know what it is, but...
It must be, like, amazing then.
Because all the guppy stuff sucks ass.
Okay, so watch this.
We're going to teleport.
No, not yet.
Wait, wait, wait.
Not yet, not yet.
Uh... where's this item I had?
Is it up here?
Aha!
Look at that.
Now we go back.
I'm going to re-roll this son of a gun.
Oh, yeah.
Actually, wait a minute before I do.
Just in case there's an item in here.
Wait, where am I right now?
Okay, yeah, look!
I am in the gray secret!
Yeah!
Not bad.
Oh, right, you wanted those.
I'm sorry, I should have let you pick them up.
Not bad, buddy.
Not bad.
Uh... go down.
Here we go.
Magic 8.
Ah, shot speed is useless.
But chance of planetariums is cool.
And a random card.
Two red hearts.
Useless.
The lovers.
Ooh, a pill.
Ah, fuck.
Wait a minute.
Oh, I could have maybe re-rolled this!
The door was open!
Because we had the fucking head!
Dammit!
Dammit, it was almost perfect.
I almost nailed everything about that progression or series of events.
I even have batteries!
Wait.
I was about to say, we can re-roll again, but that's not a re-roll, that's a teleport.
Jesus Christ.
Oh my God, let me see.
So next one is shot, then we have that one, that one, that one, that one.
I don't know what those two are.
I wonder if the planetarium can retroactively spawn now that I got this on this floor.
Let's try it.
Are you ready, kids?
Oh, of course I'm here!
Oh, obviously!
I forgot about this room.
Whoops.
Dammit!
Okay, well...
I should have quit when I was ahead before.
Like, I was doing great, and then all of a sudden, you know...
The plane crashed.
Into the ocean.
Just like that.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
The fool!
I almost had you, didn't I?
Where's the fool?
Where you at?
It's up here.
Dude, the plane went into the ocean, and then it came up through the waters again.
And now it's soaring high up in the sky.
Hell yeah.
That's good!
Now we're leaving.
Also, before we do...
Oh gosh, stop.
This...
Dude, the screenshot is just not working in this game.
Stop!
No!
There we go.
I got it.
Oh, it's very tiny.
There we go.
Nice.
I need to look into why it's doing that.
It's like I need to press the button three times before it works.
Okay.
So far, so good, man.
I feel like I'm nailing things here.
This is going great.
Yep, yep, yep.
This is only the fourth floor.
How?
Feels like I've been playing this run for two hours.
Ooh, I love my pills.
Hey!
Actually useless, but still.
Unless that affects my little initial push here.
You know?
I wonder, though, if I'm in close range and I do this...
Maybe this is better DPS.
Ah, probably like that... was better.
Ah, but then I need to stay at longer range, otherwise, you know.
Ah, I don't want to take damage.
I'm having trouble locating my character again.
There's too many familiars.
This weird heart.
Oh, I cannot even take it!
I need a red heart for that.
Aha!
I cannot...
You've got to be careful here, because...
If I close range this guy, I'm going to destroy him.
That's actually kind of annoying.
There's no easy way to deal with it.
I guess my little familiar.
Okay, no more.
Let's go find a shop instead.
Wow, a chest!
Ha ha ha!
Holy shit!
Dude, destroying rocks is...
Good.
Oh wait, I almost didn't pick those up.
Close one.
I mean, I would have seen it on the map, right?
Come on now, guys.
More pills!
Useless for me.
Oh, I'm going to have a field day in here.
Uh, we do it at range though.
Yep, make me smaller.
Keep the full.
Wait, is it even smaller?
No, what's that?
Hey!
Dude!
These pills are amazing!
Okay, that was it.
Lovely.
It's AWAS.
I knew it was.
Dude, did...
Did you just get better luck on this character?
It's confirmed.
Drag brass.
Blood bags!
No, blood bombs!
Plus one health, heals four red hearts.
Bomb explosions spawn in a puddle of damaging creep.
And allows placing bombs when bomb counters ensue...
Oh, at the cost of health.
I like it.
Plus one health is always massive.
Don't forget the card.
Burnt penny?
Can I just spawn a bomb each time?
Oh, is that the same one I had last time?
You know what?
Let's keep that.
We don't have that many bombs, so...
Yeah.
And when we have cleared every room, we're going to start using the teleporter.
He's going to get fatter, look.
What is that?
AWAS again!
Brother!
Stop!
Actually, no, keep going!
I love it.
I love my AWAS.
Boom.
I'm buying pills.
Yeah.
Pills are good.
Let's find a sus floor decoration.
No, that's just... I feel like that's not a decoration.
Wait, why did this open?
Oh, so what?
Oh, that's interesting.
So if you've been in there before, it just sort of... reveals.
Whoopsie daisy.
That was horrible.
Floor decoration, no?
Dude, that's nothing.
I see none.
This grass.
Come on.
Awww!
That's such a crap shoot, man.
Also, what was this?
Mom's contacts?
More range, chance to fire, okay.
I don't think that does anything for me, though.
Destroy this guy.
We're going to do the boss now, and then we're going to start teleporting around.
Ah,
wait, wait, wait.
We're missing one room here.
Oh, God.
Safety cap.
Ooh, I like the pills!
Definitely taking that.
That's huge.
Really nice.
Oh, let me see the order on this again.
Boss, so we got to clear that.
Then we go to Grey.
We have not found that.
Okay, so Grey's next, and then after that...
Shop, treasure, spike.
Shop, treasure...
I don't think there's a spike.
So that means...
Dice, if it exists, and then, okay, then it's going to be curse.
Got it.
Boss, we do manually, though.
It's Vistula.
That went really well.
Oh, he's scared?
Got him.
Money equals power and...
Here we go.
Now, that is exciting.
This is also exciting.
I would say both.
Yeah, I'm taking this.
I'm taking that.
We're going to use this.
Then we're going to take this.
We're going to do...
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
We have an issue.
No, we don't.
We got goat heads.
Okay, we have no issue.
Go!
What?
Okay, it's the other secret room.
Man, I really want to step.
Except I have no red heart, so rip on that.
Okay, go back and grab the other...
item, the Bible.
That's up here.
We're rolling with the Bible from now on.
This is how we're going to sustain our HP.
Love that item.
It is in my top...
I don't even know how many.
Ten items, probably.
It's very good.
It's a good item.
I think I may have seen some batteries somewhere.
Or was that last run?
Alright, let's just leave.
I feel good.
We have the Fool.
We got all my fat familiars here.
Oh, yeah.
We're going.
Necropolis.
I gotta be careful with those bombs.
Dude, I think my close range does more damage than the long one.
Wait, am I not hitting him?
Okay.
I think I may like...
This essays more than the standard one.
So far, at least.
Not entirely sure yet.
I'm still deciding.
Shit.
Where's the other guy?
There he is.
Use the book.
Should be easy.
Wait, why am I doing this?
That's why I'm doing it, baby.
Hey, more luck.
Three luck now.
The boss is here.
Well, this could be Mom.
I forgot where we are in the scheme of things.
I don't think it's the Mom, but it could be.
And I'm not entirely sure.
I should keep track of that better.
I'm just going to play it safe and not enter yet.
Just lost a black heart there.
No, I'm not going to go in the curse room.
Jesus Christ.
I feel like I'm just gambling a little bit when I do this.
This room is not good for my brain.
A card.
The lovers.
Not that I need that, but okay.
Oh, frick.
That's fine.
Oh, there's spikes on them.
I don't like that, actually.
No, thanks.
If I find invincibility, then I may do it.
Nice.
There we go.
I'm going to leave this be for now.
I don't know why.
It's just because I'm unsure.
So we're just going to move on.
Let's see.
Anything worth exchanging my two point something damage for?
Oh, the PhD.
Oh, the mystery gift.
Dude, we're going to go to the devil room with the mystery gift.
That's the plan, but not yet.
Only when we get to boss.
Down.
I love the close range.
You do before the long range.
It is so frickin' satisfying.
Blow it up.
Oh, okay.
Check this out.
We're going to do this now.
Watch.
Hey, come on.
That's cool.
Oh, he got really big now.
Look at him.
My guy is fat now.
Dude, being able to destroy the blue flames as well is going to be insane.
Didn't even think about that.
A chili.
A chance of fighting tears to also fire a sliding red flame projectile.
I got three luck, though.
This is going to go hard.
The stars.
Treasure room.
If there is a planetarium...
I think I'm going to do it.
Ah, okay.
Too bad.
It doesn't exist.
Ah!
Ran through it like an idiot.
Minus one log, no thanks.
I feel
like I haven't gotten charges on my Black Bible yet in a while.
Feels like forever ago.
Okay, so we found white...
question mark.
Let's go to the boss.
It's time.
Oi, yo, yo, almost stepped on those.
Here we go.
It's the bloat!
But not mom yet.
Dude, when he lands, I can just use my... to deflect the projectiles, right?
It's so cool.
Three blue ones for that one, huh?
Uh, wait, before I decide that.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
The gift!
The gift?
We're grabbing the gift?
Completely forgot about that until I saw that, uh, devil room.
Oh, I could also... dude, dude, dude, hold on, hold up!
Gimme that!
Wait, there's a pill!
Nice!
Yeah...
Let's go back.
Let me read this.
The gift is consumed to spawn a random pedestal item from the current room's item pool.
Got it, okay.
What did it say otherwise?
He has to spawn the poop or a lump of coal instead.
Oh, so if I...
if I don't do it in a...
special room, I guess?
Okay.
Or maybe it's just a random chance that, hey, you may actually just get that, you know?
Because it is a gift, and sometimes...
you get a shitty gift.
Uh, let's see.
Oh my god.
Who would pick these up, man?
They all suck!
We're definitely using this in here.
Boink!
Yeah, wait!
We have a real PhD and a false one at the same time.
Yo!
I'll take that.
That's a lot of extra damage.
Hell yeah.
That's crazy.
Not even the devil dude here can be affected by my special...
close-range attack.
Boink!
I think I'll take this one.
Yep.
Thank you.
Much appreciated.
And we're off!
We got the fool!
We got both PhDs!
Let me... oh wait, so how does that work now?
Wait, did I just fuck this up by overriding my...
good PhD with the bad PhD?
Oh, shit.
Wait, wait, wait.
So...
False PhD.
I think I may have overwritten this effect, man.
Oh, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
I regret taking it.
But it is 3.18 damage, right?
And what else does it say?
Converge most good...
Ah, but wait a minute!
So I made all pills good with this, right?
So now all pills are good.
But then, this one comes in and converts all good pill effects...
into... oh wait, that's bad for me.
I forgot the rest of that sentence.
Wait, this is actually even worse than I thought.
Consuming any stat down pill will also...
I mean, okay, the damage could be helpful, right?
Okay.
Do I want to step in the...
Oh, I also got to get my fucking Bible before I leave.
I have to make sure to get that.
Bible and... I'm not going to step in there, actually.
I'm going to stick to my current hearts.
I'm going to play it safe.
Take the Bible and we have zero coins.
Give me that.
Would actually love to get this one as well.
The blue heart.
I don't think... Oh, I can actually maybe get it.
Check it out.
Wait, why am I using a bomb when I can just blow it up with my hands?
Well, it didn't give me any money anyway.
All right, I think we are leaving.
Nothing else to do, right?
Let me check.
There's a pill in the bottom right, but that was a bad pill.
We got the Fool.
We got the Bible.
Check.
I think we're good.
Time to get out of here.
I know I'm spending like 10 years on each floor, but...
It is what it is.
Okay, go.
Let's go.
So now it's time for mom.
It's mom now.
The door is here.
Get... use the Bible.
Immediately.
God, I love the close range attack.
It is so fun to weave, bob and weave between close and long.
Yo, huge.
Nice.
I think the extra range does affect my close range as well.
More luck is good for me, because I got the...
the one effect that relies on luck.
I forgot which one of those.
A beggar.
Sure.
How much red hearts?
I ain't got that.
Oh yeah, the flame.
Get in here.
Holy beggars!
One of them has no hair.
This guy has some hair.
This guy is old and has no hair.
I've got... No, I've got 14 keys.
Let's give him some.
I almost misread it again.
Hey!
Coins for you!
Redistributing wealth amongst the beggars.
Come on.
Butterbean.
Nah, no thanks.
Battery?
Hurry.
Yeah.
Come on.
Boom!
Okay, I'm gonna save it for a little bit later.
I also don't want to use all my money, just because it's also extra damage, right?
We're gonna strike a balance with that.
Oh, don't forget the Fool, of course.
Imagine leaving that behind.
Even smaller, I'm not gonna be able to see my character and I'm gonna hate it.
But it does help with dodging projectiles, assuming I can see my character.
The knife is bigger than I am!
Nice!
Holy shit.
Money!
Oh, you want some money?
Go grab him, buddy.
Wait, can he get even bigger?
I thought he was at his final form.
You're gonna scooch across the screen now?
That guy's annoying.
Sick.
Pible-tracked.
Wait, that's Eternal Hearts.
I don't think I want those, actually.
Now that I have this Bible.
Like the Black Bible.
Grant's flight for the room, okay.
Keep that in mind in case we encounter something that needs that.
Oh my god.
I gotta let this guy collect coins.
How are you hitting me?
Mom's perfume.
More tears, chance to fire beer tears.
Yo, more with luck.
We got a lot of luck.
Any chance on tear things is good for us.
Oh, I like this.
That was bad for me.
Unlucky.
Voodoo head.
The additional curse rooms.
I don't know about that.
There is improved rewards, it says.
You know what?
Let's just experiment with that.
We do have the Black Bible, right?
And we have a way to generate more black hearts with the battery generator up here.
So we can experiment.
Yeah, let's head to that room because we have a couple blue hearts.
We can use those.
I legitimately can't see my character anymore.
It's going to fuck me over and I'm gonna hate it.
That's right.
The voodoo head may not have had a chance to affect this floor yet.
I can totally see that being a thing.
Huge!
I don't want luck down.
Ah, but wait a minute, it gives 0.6 damage.
Nah, it's not worth it.
I think my DPS is bigger if I go up close and just do this.
I'm not even joking.
Another fool.
Still missing one.
I forgot to take a picture last floor of the map.
No, actually check this.
What is that?
It causes tears to pulse in size.
How does that even work with me?
That does nothing.
Useless.
At least I think so.
We got a couple of rooms left and I also want to go back and get a bit more energy.
Go here.
I don't think that way.
We're gonna find an AWAS in here.
Watch.
I have predictive powers of a god.
Damn it!
More luck though.
It's sick.
And there it is.
Holy money.
Maybe I'll take the big one.
You can take the smaller ones.
Let's go.
Okay.
Holy heels, all red hearts.
That's useless for me.
You can grab that one.
There you go.
Are you gonna be bigger or what?
Do you have a final form?
I think we're ready.
Yeah.
No, wait, wait.
I can do that after.
We're ready.
Dude, I have crazy damage.
What the fuck?
Holy shit.
I freaking nailed her.
Wow.
The pact.
Two black hearts.
I mean, this one is a no-brainer, I think.
This one is a black card and... I mean, honestly, I feel like I should take both.
I think I can afford to do it, especially with the battery, dude.
I'm taking both.
Fuck it.
I'm going fuck wild up in this.
Now we go back and battery up.
Boink.
We don't go through the door yet.
We are gonna go all the way up to the arkard.
This way.
And we're gonna get some battery going.
Lovely.
Fill me up.
Before I go, go.
We're gonna sacrifice some damage doing this, but it's okay.
Our damage is... No!
I mean, that's pretty good, I guess.
I got 10 keys.
We can give him some keys, okay?
Oh yeah, pick him up, pick him up.
I want this guy to get fatter.
Wait, what's happening?
Did he just poop up some stuff for me?
Temperance.
Okay, no more now.
Oh, that's huge!
Okay, dude.
Thank you.
I'll see you later.
I'm gonna blow you up.
And a luck!
I do declare.
I'm good now.
Thanks.
Now we leave.
What was the entrance?
Over here-ish?
It's right here?
Yep.
Double-check everything.
We could grab a card somewhere, probably.
There's a card down here.
Maybe I want to bring that.
I'm optimizing so much, it's actually making... it's disgusting in a lot of ways, you know?
It truly does disgust me.
The min-maxing that is taking place right now.
I'm gonna donate money.
No, I'm not!
Money equals power.
We need it.
Let's go.
Let's go!
We're leaving.
Oh, no, this way, this way.
I think we're done here.
Boom!
Oh!
Nice!
I mean, now we're ready.
We are so ready for this.
Gehenna 2!
I can't see my character!
Fuck.
Rosary bead.
You know what?
I kind of want to see an angel.
We can we can try that, but I have no... What's happening?
I got grabbed!
A tiny hand grabbed me.
I'm not sure this guy's gonna grow any bigger.
Seems to us... hit his limit there.
Oh, don't take my stuff.
Less damage.
Fuck.
Hello!
That seems really good.
Hello?
Oh!
Yo, that's... I'm loving that.
I really am loving that.
That is huge.
Just for three damage?
I take that deal any day.
Any day of the week.
That was actually a waste just now.
I shouldn't have done that.
So we have the two curse rooms.
Let's make use of it, huh?
I didn't mean to pick that up.
That was a mistake.
Alright, this is just insane what's happening here.
There's too many black hearts.
Yes, we'll take that.
Just to remove the blue one, right?
Oh, they weren't kidding with the rewards!
More luck?
Hank, man, that's the one I had.
Oh, crap.
What's this one?
Cursed eye.
No, thank you.
I'm good, son.
I didn't mean to do that.
Thank God I didn't double dip on it, huh?
Oh, my... The close range is probably also double, isn't it?
Look at it.
It looks like a double, actually.
Yeah.
More speed.
Oh, I should have hit that button.
When there's a button, you hit it.
That's the rule.
Not sure how I took damage, but... Okay.
Whoa.
Oh, I see.
Oh!
Dude, I...
No, thanks.
I have my own shoot, and it's way better.
Ah, bad timing on that.
That was totally me.
This is so much fun.
We got a step room.
I'm almost tempted to do it.
Um, ghost?
Yeah.
Oh, that's gonna conjoined!
It
falls!
Look at my close range attack.
It's massive.
That's amazing.
I don't know if I should keep the flight or not.
Maybe... Yeah, actually, you know, that could be really helpful.
The Hank man.
I mean, I'm just playing Space Invaders now.
This is the name of the game.
Also, a great way to check for secrets like this.
The tower.
Whoops.
My bad.
I beg her.
Oh wait, this is the fucked up thingy.
Pause is here.
Are we ready?
There's a shot that I missed.
Holy crap.
Wait a sec.
I'm going to the shop.
Here.
No, I don't want that.
You know, it does say 0% Angel, so maybe this is better.
I'll keep the safety cap.
Occasionally spawns a bad...
That's good, sons!
I did not mean to destroy that.
That was a pure frickin' accident.
Damn.
Oh well.
It happens.
More range?
I don't care.
Also, what's the secret room status?
There's no status.
We have found none.
I'm not happy with that.
Maybe there are none in Gehenna.
Because I've been blowing up every single room like so much.
Never mind.
It's here.
This guy's not gonna get fatter.
He poops out things, though.
I'm gonna check this room.
I think I'd rather have... Yeah, just stick with the Hank man.
Hank man is good.
This one I checked already.
There's nothing in here.
I mean, it could be over here.
No?
I don't know.
Let's go.
Oh, right.
Huge.
Let's do it!
Wish me luck!
Uh... Oh, that's weird.
Savings are gone!
They are mega gone.
That was so satisfying.
Oh, treasure room.
Ah, but yeah.
Okay, we're not gonna find anything, I guess.
These are the... Ah, I can't believe I stepped on that!
Shit.
I need more heart before I move on.
I think I can afford to do it.
Especially with that battery.
That's kind of a big battery.
I'm gonna serve that or save that.
Um, you know, at this point, why not?
Give me more damage.
Two of diamonds?
Doubles?
Core?
Yo, damage!
Not bad.
Give me that back.
Give me a black heart.
We're gonna go in here.
Wrap this.
Black heart.
Then we move on.
Fucking optimized.
Wait, what?
Oh.
That was bad.
Why didn't I just do it from range?
Speaking of range.
I'll come back for that, maybe.
Push pin!
He has to fire tears that are piercing and spectral.
Increase with luck?
Yeah.
Wait, wait.
They are already piercing and spectral.
That's a waste.
That's a total waste.
I don't think we can find secrets here.
Tower.
I want to get a really good card, you know?
Like that one!
That's a really good one.
Plus two damage is gonna go hard.
I didn't... I shouldn't have used that.
That was a waste.
Uh,
was that last shot?
Yeah, that's good.
I'd rather take that.
Uh, let's take the battery then.
We'll get one more and then we go.
Man, I can't wait to see what happens at the end of this.
I really hope we make it this time.
You know, being too close to the wall is actually kind of risky because the conjoined is gonna blow me up, you know?
Insane.
As soon as I drop below max health, the game is like, I got you bro.
This guy is not gonna grow bigger.
He's just consuming for the for the love of the game at this point.
Everything's clean.
Uh, go.
I'm double checking every floor just in case there is something on one of the floors, you know?
You never know.
Ah, damn it.
Take it.
Okay, I got 69 coins.
Nice.
Use the bible.
Whoa.
Another puddle of creep.
What's the point of this room?
What?
No, thanks.
I'm leaving.
Gotta get one more heart though.
No.
I take the coins.
I need damage.
Uh, yeah.
Very good for me.
Okay.
Uh, did I see a battery here?
No.
On we go.
You need to repent.
You need to confess your sins and become saved.
Let his light inside you cleanse your soul.
You are insane.
Fucking took my money.
Taking this too far, how you sound.
Pray with me.
Pray for your solution.
That was damage for me.
Come
on.
All right, there it is, but I need more.
If only he was all red hearts.
Sure.
Oi, yo, yo.
Dude, I'm going to have so much trouble with the small character here soon.
I really hope it's not going to fuck me.
Like I am really small or tiny.
Another heart.
Can we get one more?
It could be the difference, you know.
Shit.
Yeah.
Bad idea.
Yeah, let's blow him up.
There we go.
Thanks.
Still need one more heart though.
Well, that's okay.
Ran out of rooms.
Go up, up, up, up.
Dude, you have HP.
What the?
Wow.
Cheers up, speed down.
Oh, that's good for me.
I don't need that much speed anyway.
Yeah, that's good.
Dude, shot speed is useless for me, right?
So all those are W's.
Oh my God.
The fact that I just walk around doing this is crazy.
Why is there a heart in there?
Oh God.
Shit, I knew I was going to take damage.
I knew it.
As soon as I entered the room.
Those enemies.
That was weird.
Use this.
Cheers up, speed down.
Yeah.
Okay, we're getting a little too slow now, maybe.
Should have calmed down with that.
What the fuck is that?
Swallow a penny.
It spawns a coin each time Isaac takes damage.
I mean, this one was a chance of finding a pill.
All right, keep... I want that.
It's giving me a lot of damage.
Like, look how fast I can do this now, if need be.
Ah, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Why am I crying?
We have plenty of hearts.
I just want to have full hearts before we go, you know.
I like taking that.
This is such a good pill.
Got one more room.
Maybe one more.
And no, I think not.
That's the second time you tried to push that on me.
I reject.
Ascend.
Basement.
Oh my god, look.
No, you're alive.
Okay.
Thought you'd die.
The hell?
Get the money before he does.
Nice.
At least he's fat and slow.
Like, I can't see where my character is.
I can't even navigate this little area.
Can I destroy this?
No.
Let's do it.
I mean, at this point, it's getting ridiculous, but in a fun way.
We are so incredibly small that it's kind of funny.
I'm gonna have to try and keep it... pay attention to where my shots are landing to see where I am.
Yeah, at this point, sure.
I exchanged luck for damage.
I got plenty of luck.
I saw that coming.
Why did I do that?
That was bad.
Bad as usual.
Hey!
Okay, we're back.
We're back.
The game's got me.
Wait, I don't even need to clear anymore.
I'm full health.
I'm just doing it for the love of the game at this point.
I guess I have a full charge now.
Here we go!
Home.
Okay.
No, that's mine, bastard.
What happened?
Blow it up.
Dude, we gotta look for the outline again.
But only when we have that item.
I should just be bombing every single wall here, man.
Okay.
Uh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
That's gonna take us to three out of mother.
Dude, I don't even know what's happening.
We have, like, a poison knife in addition to the normal knife.
I don't know why.
Here we go.
Ladies and gentlemen, this is it.
Hold on to your ass and goggles.
Shit's about to kick off against dogma.
Actually, it's the TV.
Oh, shit.
Use this immediately.
You know what?
Let me try and get close and just spam.
It may actually be better.
I'm not sure.
It's very close, I think.
Dude, full HP?
Come on.
So far, so good.
We gotta mark him.
Oh, bastard.
I can't see my tank!
Okay, there I am.
I see myself.
I got him, I got him.
Locked in.
Target locked.
All right, all right.
I'm gonna save my card for the next phase.
Oh, god.
Where am I?
Fuck!
Goddammit.
I see, I see.
I'm here, I'm here, I'm here.
I can't... I lose track of my character immediately.
I can't fucking stand the fact that I can't see my character, man.
I lost, like, five hearts to that just now.
Okay, let's do this.
It's about to charge me or something.
Oh, god.
No!
Okay, so we alternate.
I see.
Alternation, alternation.
Are you gonna drop batteries for me or what?
Right, okay, I remember that, I remember that.
Are
you dead?
Are you dead?
Next one.
Use Bible.
Oh, devil!
Use the devil.
Fucking devil.
Oh, right, right.
Horizontal, horizontal.
Fuck, man!
I die, it's over, man.
I can't win!
Oh, god fucking damn it, man.
Not like this!
I'm gonna rage quit on that one.
That's a rage quit.
That's a definite rage quit.
Fucking hell, man.
Oh, I need wafer.
I need wafer on that one.
That's rough.
And the worst part is, as soon as I saw the attacks the first two times, you know, I was like, oh, yeah, that's right, that's how that works.
I need to remember for next time the types of attacks these guys have, you know, the horizontal ones.
Like, I could have dodged those.
I know I could have.
That was so bad.
What's up, guys?
Meebskitten!
Good to see you, man.
20 community subs.
Thank you very much.
You know, you're at quite a bit at this point.
Do you know how many you're at?
It's kind of crazy.
You're like, all the way up top, you know?
260.
Oh, I can't believe it.
I feel like it was a good run, though.
I learned that I have a new favorite character.
And I hate to say it, but the title of this next mod is going to be, this is now my favorite character, because I keep getting new ones.
This one is better than a Seizel, I think.
The close range shotgun, followed by the charge up range of the attack is Chef's Kiss.
What a feeling.
What's up, potato Greenland, milu, fitting name.
Thank you.
I've watched enough of your shit to warrant the gift subs, trust.
Thank you so much.
I can't thank you enough, man.
It really means a lot to me.
I'm glad you're enjoying it that much.
But just know that you don't need to do that, you know?
Like, you've already given so much.
You just sit back, watch the stream, relax, you know, from now on.
You've earned the right to kick back on the couch with a bag of potato chips and enjoy the show.
Enjoy watching me suffer.
New favorite character V2, real this time.
No clickbait.
I should do that.
After life, after having two Seizels, it's quite amazing.
It feels like, you know, before this, I really wanted to pick a Seizel all the time because maybe for you it's different.
But for me, I don't get bored with a Seizel.
I just don't.
I think it's fun every time.
I'm having a blast every time I pick a Seizel.
But now I feel a little less guilty about picking a Seizel because it's the newest Seizel.
We haven't had this Seizel before, you know?
So now I feel better about doing it.
Which alt character are you most interested to get next?
What?
Oh, you mean the E thing?
I don't know.
I didn't even realize all of them had one.
But I guess I do now.
You haven't seen a Seizel 3.
Dude, I can't wait until a Seizel 3 comes out.
Would you like your life more if you had three?
I think I would actually.
I think I would like my life way more if I had more Seizels.
Like, there's no upper limit on that.
20 Seizels.
20 Seizels is what I need.
It's just too much fun to either fly around and shoot shit from behind rocks or be at a long range and just plink away at enemies, you know?
Or when they're close, you're like pushing away projectiles.
Speaking of, man, I think I should have utilized my close range projectile fort with the uh with the alternate Seizel.
At the end there, I think I could have dodged some of those attacks if I had timed it right.
That would have been really nice.
I didn't think about that.
In fact, I can just sit in one spot and spam the button, right?
And I fart away everything that comes close to me.
Oh, I should have thought of that.
Oh my gosh.
If I'm close to the boss and I just on the button, right?
I push away all this shit and I do damage.
Oh my goodness.
I think I just discovered the winning strategy.
Are you glad you made it home?
Made it to home with a Seizel the first time you could unlock a Seizel too?
I mean, for sure.
I'm glad everything happened here.
Dogma and Beast are really easy once you figure out the patterns.
Dogma is not that hard.
I don't know who Beast is.
Is that the one I just fought?
I didn't pay attention to the name of the boss.
Galad Maxer.
I mean, yeah.
Oh, that's the name of him?
Okay, okay.
I see.
Minus 12th Street.
No, no, no.
That's not true.
That ain't true.
You didn't see that.
That's not true.
I'm totally not gonna play off stream before next time and get the win streak to one.
No, no, no.
I'm not gonna do that.
I would never do that.
It's all gonna be live on stream, of course.
Come on.
Mr. Beast.
This is actually kind of a nice song that's playing, right?
I think it's dad singing.
Like the voice?
Yeah,
it is.
Who else would it be?
Dude, what if we are actually dad, you know?
But in the past, and there's like time travel.
That would be awesome.
I don't think that's true, though.
I would love that.
Why did you finish?
I did not finish my food.
Listen, man.
I rage quit a little bit at the end there, okay?
It was a mild rage quit, I will say.
It was a happy rage quit.
Because I was actually somewhat satisfied with that run.
All in all.
If I had won that run, I probably would have played one more.
But I got to calm down a little bit, too.
Yeah, it was like, yeah, one hour 30 minutes and then just die within two minutes.
Ooh.
Is the rupalism out of time?
It's not actually.
I don't know what time it is.
I need to think on that.
I don't know what to make.
Disappoint quit.
I like that one.
Okay, practice for the boss.
Next one is a win.
Trust.
Exactly, Frank.
That's the way to look at it.
Not only that, but I learned how to play the newest Azel.
Yeah.
And that right there is actually more important, I think.
Just knowing how to utilize the character.
Yeah, I know it's gonna take some tries to get the new boss, but it would be nice to... I'm just... I'm too excited to see what happens next, you know, because they're building it up with all this dialogue on all these floors until you get to this boss.
And then I really want to see what happens next, you know?
Next time.
Next time I'll do it.
I got to like minus 20 to beat that boss with Jacob.
The boss is pretty hard.
I mean, Jacob is pretty hard to play.
If you're talking about the... you're talking about Jacob and Azel, right?
That thing is nuts.
I mean, I understand if you had a minus 20 on that.
I would forgive minus 50 on that.
So, yeah.
You beat Mother first try, so it's only... Did I actually... The first time I beat... Was that the first or second stream?
Wait, did I actually beat that first try?
That's kind of crazy if I did.
Because that boss is not easy.
Oh, right, Mother.
Sorry.
Yes.
Oh, Mother.
Yeah, that's right.
That's different.
True.
Mom is different.
Mom is the first one.
Mother is the one... That's actually so funny that they do that.
One HP clutch.
Yeah, those are the best.
Jacob and the hitbox.
Is that... Were you making a Jacob and the juice thing?
No, wait, that's imagining brands in my head now, for some reason.
Jacob and hitbox is what the community calls them.
Oh, I see.
Makes sense.
I understand why they do that.
Oh, yeah.
Mom's heart.
Mother.
Many different variations.
There's also it lives, which is also Mother, I guess, in a way.
You need to hear this.
This is risky.
Jacob and Esau, but instead of Jacob, it's a sasle.
And instead of Esau, it's tainted a sasle.
Dude, sign me the fuck up.
I would love that.
Oh, but wait, wait, wait.
So one of them flies, the other one doesn't?
Ooh, that's gonna be... You're gonna get distinct really fast with that setup.
That doesn't sound like a good time, man.
It sounds good on paper, but then in reality, I think you're gonna hate it.
Ah, will you though?
Because, yeah, actually you will, because one of them has very short range, the other one has brimstone.
So it's just gonna be a nightmare.
Next stream, local multiplayer, using hands and feet to play as aisles.
I'd rather just clone myself and have that person play on another computer.
What would the interactions be between me and my clone?
I think that that could be entertaining.
I could be like, wait, did I get everything on this floor?
The other one, yeah, I think we got everything.
And then we both go fuck afterwards, you know?
Because we always forget we're the same brain.
Or would it actually be a net positive?
Would you play a sasle one or two?
I would play two.
I wouldn't trust my clone to handle two.
Because I have the experience with the two.
He only has experience with the one.
Double dementia.
Well, two negatives cancel out and become positive, right?
Twice the dementia is twice the fun.
Oh, no, there's online achievements you need to get to 100%.
I don't know if I like that.
I feel like you should be able to do everything single-player.
I mean, I have no aspirations to ever reach 100%.
I'm just saying, in practice, you know?
Only a couple, okay.
You're no longer at... Oh, you were a hundred third share row.
Oh, that must suck.
I mean, I've never been the biggest achievement guy, you know?
So, but I can relate to the perfectionist side of it and the slightly and mildly OCD part of it.
Of having had a hundred and now having, I don't know, like 95 or whatever it is.
I can see that.
Also, I'm slowly approaching the achievements in what's it called?
What's that game called?
The Stanley Parable.
The one with don't log in for years at a time or something, remember?
I'm working on that.
I haven't logged in in a while.
Five years, yes.
I think it's... we got to approach like two years at this point.
Ten years.
That's crazy.
Okay.
What is this hype train anyway?
Oh, it's complete now, I see.
What the fuck is that achievement?
Never placed.
It's an achievement where if you don't log into the game for five years, meaning you don't launch the game from Steam, that's how you get the achievement.
I think it's called Go Touch Grass or something.
It was kind of funny.
It's like an anti don't play my game, you know?
It's a joke, but it's really not a joke in a way.
People should just get it automatically if you hadn't bought the game for the first five or ten years since it came out.
You technically didn't play it for that amount of time, right?
That's only fair, in my opinion.
But then you wouldn't play it for ten years and then you would launch it.
No, no, you would get the achievement immediately and then you would... yeah, yeah, okay.
And you complete that achievement by not touching grass for five years in other games.
I guess so.
Alright, I'm gonna go guys, thank you for watching.
I think we did a lot of good stuff in this stream even though we didn't get a win.
Wait, we got one win.
We got one win and we learned a lot, so that's important.
Thanks for watching.
Have a lalalalalala